Mental Health Association in New York State, Inc. (MHANYS) Records apap131
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Predecessor Organizations, 1879-1960; 1; 2.0 cubic ft.
  - State Charities Aid Association, 1879-1951; 1.1; 1.5 cubic ft.
    - Committee on Mental Hygiene, New York City, Executive Committee Minutes, 1929-1933 (Box 1 (1-Predecessor Organizations), Folder 30)
    - Committee on Mental Hygiene, New York City, Executive Committee Minutes, 1928-1936 (Box 1 (1-Predecessor Organizations), Folder 31)
    - Committee on Mental Hygiene, New York City, Executive Committee Minutes, 1934-1945 (Box 1 (1-Predecessor Organizations), Folder 32)
    - Committee on Mental Hygiene, New York City, Executive Committee Minutes, 1937-1946 (Box 1 (1-Predecessor Organizations), Folder 33)
    - Committee on Mental Hygiene, New York City, Minutes, 1938-1941 (Box 1 (1-Predecessor Organizations), Folder 34)
    - Committee on Mental Hygiene, New York City, Minutes, 1942-1946 (Box 1 (1-Predecessor Organizations), Folder 35)
    - Committee on Mental Hygiene, New York City, Reports, 1942-1944 (Box 1 (1-Predecessor Organizations), Folder 36)
    - Committee on Mental Hygiene, New York City, Subcommittee Minutes, 1933-1939 (Box 1 (1-Predecessor Organizations), Folder 37)
    - Correspondence, 1879-1885 (Box 1 (1-Predecessor Organizations), Folder 38-40)
    - County Visiting Committee, 1896 (Box 1 (1-Predecessor Organizations), Folder 41)
    - External Publications, 1911-1939 (Box 1 (1-Predecessor Organizations), Folder 42-43)
    - Fassett Batcheller Bill Constitution, 1889-1935 (Box 1 (1-Predecessor Organizations), Folder 44)
    - Pamphlets, 1880-1899 (Box 1 (1-Predecessor Organizations), Folder 45)
    - Pamphlets, 1900-1909 (Box 1 (1-Predecessor Organizations), Folder 46)
    - Pamphlets, 1910-1919 (Box 1 (1-Predecessor Organizations), Folder 47)
    - Pamphlets, 1920-1929; 1944 (Box 2 (1-Predecessor Organizations), Folder 1)
    - Pamphlets, 1930-1939; 1944 (Box 2 (1-Predecessor Organizations), Folder 2)
    - Reprints, Homer Folks, 1890-1900 (Box 2 (1-Predecessor Organizations), Folder 3)
    - Reprints, Homer Folks, 1900-1915 (Box 2 (1-Predecessor Organizations), Folder 4)
    - Reprints, Homer Folks, 1915-1940 (Box 2 (1-Predecessor Organizations), Folder 5)
    - "Six Lectures on Mental Hygiene with Special Reference to Child Guidance and Social Adjustment of the Adult, Program, Lectures, 1928 (Box 2 (1-Predecessor Organizations), Folder 6)
    - Special Committee on Provision for the Feeble-Minded, "The Feeble Minded in New York", 1911 (Box 2 (1-Predecessor Organizations), Folder 7)
    - Special Study Committee Report on Relation of SCAA and State Committee on Councils and Chests, 1958 (Box 2 (1-Predecessor Organizations), Folder 8)
    - State Charities Aid Association Milestones, 1929-1946 (Box 2 (1-Predecessor Organizations), Folder 9)
    - State Government, 1887-1926 (Box 2 (1-Predecessor Organizations), Folder 10)
    - State Mental Institutions, 1889-1935 (Box 2 (1-Predecessor Organizations), Folder 11)
    - Strong Commission, 1916 (Box 2 (1-Predecessor Organizations), Folder 12)
    - Subcommittee on After Care of Insane, Minutes, 1906-1907 (Box 2 (1-Predecessor Organizations), Folder 13)
    - Subcommittee on After Care of Insane, Minutes, 1908-1910 (Box 2 (1-Predecessor Organizations), Folder 14)
    - Temporary Commission on State Hospital Problems, 1942-1943 (Box 2 (1-Predecessor Organizations), Folder 15)
    - Temporary Commission on State Hospital Problems, 1942-1944 (Box 2 (1-Predecessor Organizations), Folder 16)
    - Upstate and Metropolitan Sections of the SCAA, Minutes, 1951 (Box 2 (1-Predecessor Organizations), Folder 17)
    - Visiting Committees, Reports, 1932-1934 (Box 2 (1-Predecessor Organizations), Folder 18)
    - Visiting Committees, Reports, 1935-1936 (Box 2 (1-Predecessor Organizations), Folder 19)
    - Visiting Committees, Reports, 1937-1939 (Box 2 (1-Predecessor Organizations), Folder 20)
    - Visiting Committees, Reports, 1940-1944 (Box 2 (1-Predecessor Organizations), Folder 21)
  - New York State Society for Mental Health, 1949-1960; 1.2; 0.5 cubic ft.
    This subseries is composed of records related to the activities of the New York State Society for Mental Health (NYSSMH). Included are meeting minutes regarding the creation of NYSSMH as well as board of directors, committee, and Citizens' Advisory Group minutes; annual conference and campaign documents; and an address to NYSSMH by C. Douglas Darling.
    - Annual Conference, "Realism and Mental Health", 1952 (Box 2 (1-Predecessor Organizations), Folder 22)
    - Board of Directors Minutes, 1953-1954 (Box 2 (1-Predecessor Organizations), Folder 23)
    - Board of Directors Minutes, 1955 (Box 2 (1-Predecessor Organizations), Folder 24)
    - Board of Directors Minutes, 1956 (Box 2 (1-Predecessor Organizations), Folder 25)
    - Board of Directors Minutes, 1957 (Box 2 (1-Predecessor Organizations), Folder 26)
    - Board of Directors Minutes, 1958 (Box 2 (1-Predecessor Organizations), Folder 27)
    - Board of Directors Minutes, 1959 (Box 2 (1-Predecessor Organizations), Folder 28)
    - Board of Directors Minutes, 1960 (Box 2 (1-Predecessor Organizations), Folder 29)
    - Campaign for Mental Health, 1955-1958 (Box 2 (1-Predecessor Organizations), Folder 30)
    - Citizen's Advisory Group, 1957-1958 (Box 2 (1-Predecessor Organizations), Folder 31-32)
    - Committee on Member Organizations and Affiliations, 1956-1957 (Box 2 (1-Predecessor Organizations), Folder 33)
    - Copyrights, 1949-1957 (Box 2 (1-Predecessor Organizations), Folder 34)
    - Executive Committee, Minutes, 1952 (Box 2 (1-Predecessor Organizations), Folder 35)
    - Field Study Committee, Minutes, 1955-1957 (Box 2 (1-Predecessor Organizations), Folder 36)
    - Finance Committee, Minutes, 1955-1957 (Box 2 (1-Predecessor Organizations), Folder 37)
    - Legislative Committee, Minutes, 1955-1957 (Box 2 (1-Predecessor Organizations), Folder 38)
    - New York State Citizens Advisory Group for Mental Hospitals and Schools, Annual Meeting, 1959 (Box 2 (1-Predecessor Organizations), Folder 39)
    - Nominating Committee, Minutes, 1956-1957 (Box 2 (1-Predecessor Organizations), Folder 40)
    - Professional Advisory Committee, Minutes, 1955-1957 (Box 2 (1-Predecessor Organizations), Folder 41)
    - Program Criteria and Activities Committee, Minutes, 1955 (Box 2 (1-Predecessor Organizations), Folder 42)
    - Public Relations Committee, Minutes, 1956-1957 (Box 2 (1-Predecessor Organizations), Folder 43)
- Administration, 2
- Board of Directors, 1960-2001; 3; 3.27 cubic ft.
  - Administration, 1966-2000; 3.1; 0.25 cubic ft.
    The Administration subseries includes: directories listing members of the MHANYS board of directors and identifying MHANYS local chapters across New York State; manuals and handbooks detailing duties of members of the Board of Directors; correspondence to and from board members; and a description of a board retreat.
    - Correspondence, 1994-1996 (Box 1 (3-Board of Directors), Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1998 (Box 1 (3-Board of Directors), Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1999 (Box 1 (3-Board of Directors), Folder 3)
    - Directory, 1966-1973; 1983; 1990-1993 (Box 1 (3-Board of Directors), Folder 4)
    - Directory, 1994 (Box 1 (3-Board of Directors), Folder 5)
    - Directory, 1995-1997 (Box 1 (3-Board of Directors), Folder 6)
    - Directory, 1999 (Box 1 (3-Board of Directors), Folder 7)
    - Handbook, 1995-1996 (Box 1 (3-Board of Directors), Folder 8)
    - Manual, 1969 (Box 1 (3-Board of Directors), Folder 9)
    - Manual, Undated (Box 1 (3-Board of Directors), Folder 10)
    - Miscellaneous Information, 1983 (Box 1 (3-Board of Directors), Folder 11)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1960-2001; 3.2; 0.85 cubic ft.
    Minutes of MHANYS Board of Directors 1960-1999 covering policies of MHANYS, organizational and personnel issues, relations among MHANYS and its affiliates and the National Association of Mental Health, and various issues regarding advocacy of policies regarding mental illness.
    - Minutes, 1960 (Box 1 (3-Board of Directors), Folder 12)
    - Minutes, 1962-1963 (Box 1 (3-Board of Directors), Folder 13)
    - Minutes, 1962-1965 (Box 1 (3-Board of Directors), Folder 14)
    - Minutes, 1964 (Box 1 (3-Board of Directors), Folder 15)
    - Minutes, 1966 (Box 1 (3-Board of Directors), Folder 16-17)
    - Minutes, 1967-1969 (Box 1 (3-Board of Directors), Folder 18)
    - Minutes, 1968-1970 (Box 1 (3-Board of Directors), Folder 19)
    - Minutes, 1969-1970 (Box 1 (3-Board of Directors), Folder 20)
    - Minutes, 1970-1971 (Box 1 (3-Board of Directors), Folder 21)
    - Minutes, 1971-1972 (Box 1 (3-Board of Directors), Folder 22)
    - Minutes, 1979-1981 (Box 1 (3-Board of Directors), Folder 23)
    - Minutes, 1982-1984 (Box 1 (3-Board of Directors), Folder 24)
    - Minutes, 1985-1988 (Box 1 (3-Board of Directors), Folder 25)
    - Minutes, 1989-1990 (Box 1 (3-Board of Directors), Folder 26)
    - Minutes, 1991-1992 (Box 1 (3-Board of Directors), Folder 27)
    - Minutes, 1993-1994 (Box 1 (3-Board of Directors), Folder 28)
    - Minutes, 1994 (Box 1 (3-Board of Directors), Folder 29-30)
    - Minutes, 1995 (Box 2 (3-Board of Directors), Folder 1)
    - Minutes, 1996 (Box 2 (3-Board of Directors), Folder 2)
    - Minutes, 1997 (Box 2 (3-Board of Directors), Folder 3-4)
    - Minutes and Meetings, 1998 (Box 2 (3-Board of Directors), Folder 5-6)
    - Minutes and Meetings, 1999 (Box 2 (3-Board of Directors), Folder 7-8)
    - Minutes and Meetings, 2000-2001 (Box 2 (3-Board of Directors), Folder 9)
  - Committees, 1966-1999; 3.3; 2.17 cubic ft.
    The New York State Committee Served as the Board of Directors of MHANYS in the mid-1970s during the period when the NAMH took over operation of MHANYS. The Executive Committee of MHANYS is composed of the officers of the board and is responsible for decision-making between board meetings. Subjects covered in the Executive Committee meetings involve the full range of MHANYS organizational, policy, advocacy, and project issues. The subseries also includes minutes and other records of committees of the MHANYS board. Of particular importance is the Government Affairs Committee, which sets priorities for MHANYS regarding advocacy with the government of New York State and other public entities within the state regarding mental health policy issues. The Resource Development Committee explored fundraising opportunities and the Special Committee to study MHANYS's Future was created in 1972 to deal with a funding shortfall and dispute with the national organization are also important. The Professional Advisory Committee was a committee of psychiatrists and psychologists who advised the board of MHANYS about mental health issues.
    - Affiliate Relations Committee, 1998 (Box 2 (3-Board of Directors), Folder 10)
    - Affiliate Relations Committee, 1999 (Box 2 (3-Board of Directors), Folder 11)
    - Awards Committee, 1973 (Box 2 (3-Board of Directors), Folder 12)
    - Awards Committee, 1993-1999 (Box 2 (3-Board of Directors), Folder 13)
    - Children and Families Committee, 1994 (Box 2 (3-Board of Directors), Folder 14)
    - Community Residence Committee, 1984 (Box 2 (3-Board of Directors), Folder 15)
    - Executive Committee, 1966-1971 (Box 2 (3-Board of Directors), Folder 16)
    - Executive Committee, 1971 (Box 2 (3-Board of Directors), Folder 17)
    - Executive Committee, 1972 (Box 2 (3-Board of Directors), Folder 18-19)
    - Executive Committee, 1973 (Box 2 (3-Board of Directors), Folder 20)
    - Executive Committee, 1975-1978 (Box 2 (3-Board of Directors), Folder 21)
    - Executive Committee, 1979 (Box 2 (3-Board of Directors), Folder 22)
    - Executive Committee, 1980 (Box 2 (3-Board of Directors), Folder 23)
    - Executive Committee, 1981-1983 (Box 2 (3-Board of Directors), Folder 24)
    - Executive Committee, 1984-1985 (Box 2 (3-Board of Directors), Folder 25)
    - Executive Committee, 1986-1987 (Box 2 (3-Board of Directors), Folder 26)
    - Executive Committee, 1988-1989 (Box 2 (3-Board of Directors), Folder 27)
    - Executive Committee, 1990-1992 (Box 2 (3-Board of Directors), Folder 28)
    - Executive Committee, 1994-1995 (Box 2 (3-Board of Directors), Folder 29)
    - Executive Committee, 1998-1999 (Box 2 (3-Board of Directors), Folder 30)
    - Finance, Committee, 1978 (Box 2 (3-Board of Directors), Folder 31)
    - Finance, Committee, 1986-1990 (Box 2 (3-Board of Directors), Folder 32)
    - Finance, Committee, 1992 (Box 2 (3-Board of Directors), Folder 33-34)
    - Finance, Committee, 1993 (Box 2 (3-Board of Directors), Folder 35-39)
    - Finance, Committee, 1993 (Box 3 (3-Board of Directors), Folder 1)
    - Finance, Committee, 1993-1995 (Box 3 (3-Board of Directors), Folder 2)
    - Finance, Committee, 1995-1999 (Box 3 (3-Board of Directors), Folder 3)
    - Government Affairs Committee, 1993-1994 (Box 3 (3-Board of Directors), Folder 4)
    - Government Affairs Committee, 1995 (Box 3 (3-Board of Directors), Folder 5-8)
    - Government Affairs Committee, 1996 (Box 3 (3-Board of Directors), Folder 9-14)
    - Government Affairs Committee, 1997 (Box 3 (3-Board of Directors), Folder 15)
    - Government Affairs Committee, 1998 (Box 3 (3-Board of Directors), Folder 16-17)
    - Government Affairs Committee, 1999 (Box 3 (3-Board of Directors), Folder 18-20)
    - New York State Committee, 1974 (Box 3 (3-Board of Directors), Folder 21)
    - New York State Committee, 1975 (Box 3 (3-Board of Directors), Folder 22)
    - New York State Committee, 1978 (Box 3 (3-Board of Directors), Folder 23)
    - New York State Committee, 1979 (Box 3 (3-Board of Directors), Folder 24)
    - Nominating Committee, 1966 (Box 3 (3-Board of Directors), Folder 25)
    - Nominating Committee, 1967-1970 (Box 3 (3-Board of Directors), Folder 26)
    - Nominating Committee, 1972-1973 (Box 3 (3-Board of Directors), Folder 27)
    - Nominating Committee, 1995-1996 (Box 3 (3-Board of Directors), Folder 28-32)
    - Organizing Committee, 1975 (Box 3 (3-Board of Directors), Folder 33)
    - Personnel Committee, 1966-1971 (Box 3 (3-Board of Directors), Folder 34)
    - Planning Committee, 1998 (Box 3 (3-Board of Directors), Folder 35)
    - Planning Committee, 1999 (Box 3 (3-Board of Directors), Folder 36)
    - President's Council, 1975 (Box 3 (3-Board of Directors), Folder 37)
    - Professional Advisory Committee, 1966-1967 (Box 3 (3-Board of Directors), Folder 38)
    - Professional Advisory Committee, 1967-1968 (Box 3 (3-Board of Directors), Folder 39)
    - Professional Advisory Committee, 1969-1973 (Box 3 (3-Board of Directors), Folder 40)
    - Program and Policy Committee, 1968-1972 (Box 4 (3-Board of Directors), Folder 1)
    - Program and Policy Committee, 1972 (Box 4 (3-Board of Directors), Folder 2)
    - Program and Policy Committee, 1973 (Box 4 (3-Board of Directors), Folder 3)
    - Public Affairs Committee, 1975 (Box 4 (3-Board of Directors), Folder 4)
    - Public Affairs Committee, 1976 (Box 4 (3-Board of Directors), Folder 5)
    - Public Education Committee, note name changed to Public Information and Communications Committee in 1995, 1994-1995 (Box 4 (3-Board of Directors), Folder 6)
    - Public Relations Committee, 1965 (Box 4 (3-Board of Directors), Folder 7)
    - Resource Development Committee, 1981 (Box 4 (3-Board of Directors), Folder 8-9)
    - Resource Development Committee, 1993-1999 (Box 4 (3-Board of Directors), Folder 10)
    - Select Committee to Study NYASMH Future, 1972 (Box 4 (3-Board of Directors), Folder 11)
    - Site Visitation Committee, 1976 (Box 4 (3-Board of Directors), Folder 12)
    - Special Committee to Study NYASMH Future, 1972 (Box 4 (3-Board of Directors), Folder 13)
    - Subcommittee on Community Mental Health Center, 1966 (Box 4 (3-Board of Directors), Folder 14)
    - Subcommittee on Community Mental Health Center, 1967-1972 (Box 4 (3-Board of Directors), Folder 15)
- Meetings and Conferences, 1965-1999; 4; 1 cubic foot
  This series includes materials from MHANYS meetings with most information available about MHANYS's annual meeting. The Annual Conferences were organized by MHANYS and open to mental health professionals and the public on such topics as "Recovery in the Community" (1992), "Finding Common Ground" (1993), "It Takes a Community to Raise a Child" (1994). The Awards Luncheon focused on the presentation of an award to a public figure for services to mental health. Recipients included talk show host Montel Williams, former New York State Judge Sol Wachtler, and labor union leader Danny Donahue. Also included are materials from the Congress for Mental Health Meeting. This meeting was held annually in the 1960s and sponsored by MHANYS, the Medical Society of New York, and the American Psychiatric Association on a particular mental health topic. Copies of many of the major addresses by speakers are included.
  Arranged alphabetically.
  - Annual Conference, 1992-1993 (Box 1 (4-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 1)
  - Annual Conference, 1994 (Box 1 (4-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 2-9)
  - Annual Conference Planning, 1994 (Box 1 (4-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 10-12)
  - Annual Conference, 1995 (Box 1 (4-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 13)
  - Annual Meeting, 1967-1970 (Box 1 (4-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 14)
  - Annual Meeting, 1971 (Box 1 (4-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 15)
  - Annual Meeting, Minutes, 1971 (Box 1 (4-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 16)
  - Annual Meeting, 1972 (Box 1 (4-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 17)
  - Annual Meeting, Minutes, 1972 (Box 1 (4-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 18)
  - Annual Meeting, 1974 (Box 1 (4-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 19)
  - Annual Meeting, 1975 (Box 1 (4-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 20)
  - Annual Meeting, Minutes, 1975 (Box 1 (4-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 21)
  - Annual Meeting, Minutes, 1976 (Box 1 (4-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 22)
  - Annual Meeting, 1976 (Box 1 (4-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 23)
  - Annual Meeting, 1977 (Box 1 (4-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 24)
  - Annual Meeting, 1978 (Box 1 (4-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 25)
  - Annual Meeting, 1979 (Box 1 (4-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 26-27)
  - Annual Meeting, 1980 (Box 1 (4-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 28-29)
  - Annual Meeting, President's Report, 1980 (Box 1 (4-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 30)
  - Annual Meeting, 1981 (Box 1 (4-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 31)
  - Annual Meeting, Presentations, 1981 (Box 1 (4-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 32)
  - Annual Meeting, 1982 (Box 1 (4-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 33)
  - Annual Meeting, 1983 (Box 1 (4-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 34)
  - Annual Meeting, 1984 (Box 1 (4-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 35)
  - Annual Meeting, 1986 (Box 1 (4-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 36)
  - Annual Meeting, 1987 (Box 1 (4-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 37)
  - Annual Meeting, 1988 (Box 1 (4-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 38-41)
  - Annual Meeting Minutes, 1993 (Box 1 (4-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 42)
  - Annual Meeting Documents, 1994 (Box 1 (4-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 43)
  - Annual Meeting, 1995 (Box 1 (4-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 44)
  - Annual Meeting, 1995-1996 (Box 1 (4-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 45)
  - Annual Meeting Presentations, 1981 (Box 1 (4-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 46)
  - Awards Luncheon, 1994-2000 (Box 1 (4-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 47)
  - Congress for Mental Health, 1st and 2nd, 1965-1966 (Box 1 (4-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 48)
  - Congress for Mental Health, 3rd, 1967 (Box 1 (4-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 49)
  - Congress for Mental Health, 4th and 5th, 1968-1969 (Box 1 (4-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 50)
  - Presidents' Council, 1975 (Box 1 (4-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 51-52)
  - Special Membership Meeting, 1973 (Box 1 (4-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 53)
  - Spring Conference, 1975 (Box 1 (4-Meetings and Conferences), Folder 54)
- Affiliates, 1957-2001; 5; 2 cubic ft.
  - Regional Mental Health Associations, 1957-1996; 5.1; 1.5 cubic ft.
    This subseries includes correspondence, reports, publications, financial data, and other information generated by or for the MHANYS chapters and affiliates. Topics include funding and cost sharing between state and regional organizations and programs at the regional level.
    - Albany County, 1988-1994 (Box 1 (5-Affiliates), Folder 1)
    - Allegheny-Chemung, 1963-1996 (Box 1 (5-Affiliates), Folder 2)
    - Brooklyn Chapter, 1957-1987 (Box 1 (5-Affiliates), Folder 3)
    - Broome County, 1986; 1990-1995 (Box 1 (5-Affiliates), Folder 4)
    - Capital Region Chapter Planning, 2000 (Box 1 (5-Affiliates), Folder 5)
    - Cattaraugus County, 1986-1991 (Box 1 (5-Affiliates), Folder 6)
    - Cayuga County, 1970-1992 (Box 1 (5-Affiliates), Folder 7)
    - Chautauqua County, 1960-1975 (Box 1 (5-Affiliates), Folder 8)
    - Chautauqua County, 1984-1995 (Box 1 (5-Affiliates), Folder 9)
    - Chemung County, 1969 (Box 1 (5-Affiliates), Folder 10)
    - Chenango County, 1963-1996 (Box 1 (5-Affiliates), Folder 11)
    - Clinton County, 1963-1996 (Box 1 (5-Affiliates), Folder 12)
    - Columbia County, 1988-1992 (Box 1 (5-Affiliates), Folder 13)
    - Cortland, 1963-1996 (Box 1 (5-Affiliates), Folder 14)
    - Delaware County, 1987-1991 (Box 1 (5-Affiliates), Folder 15)
    - Dutchess County, 1993 (Box 1 (5-Affiliates), Folder 16)
    - Erie County, 1987-1991 (Box 1 (5-Affiliates), Folder 17)
    - Erie County, Board Minutes, 1957-1963 (Box 1 (5-Affiliates), Folder 18)
    - Essex, Fulton and Montgomery Counties, 1985-1996 (Box 1 (5-Affiliates), Folder 19)
    - Genesee County, 1991-1994 (Box 1 (5-Affiliates), Folder 20)
    - Greene County, 1963-1996 (Box 1 (5-Affiliates), Folder 21)
    - Jefferson County, 1987-1991 (Box 1 (5-Affiliates), Folder 22)
    - Livingston County, 1970-1991 (Box 1 (5-Affiliates), Folder 23)
    - Madison County, 1963-1996 (Box 1 (5-Affiliates), Folder 24)
    - Monroe County, 1965 (Box 1 (5-Affiliates), Folder 25)
    - Monroe and Rochester, 1985-1995 (Box 1 (5-Affiliates), Folder 26)
    - Monroe and Rochester, 1991-1995 (Box 1 (5-Affiliates), Folder 27)
    - Nassau County, 1987-1995 (Box 1 (5-Affiliates), Folder 28)
    - New York and Bronx Counties, 1986-1991 (Box 1 (5-Affiliates), Folder 29)
    - Niagara County, 1966 (Box 1 (5-Affiliates), Folder 30)
    - Niagara County, 1984-1994 (Box 1 (5-Affiliates), Folder 31)
    - Oneida County, 1991 (Box 1 (5-Affiliates), Folder 32)
    - Onondaga County, 1985-1994 (Box 1 (5-Affiliates), Folder 33)
    - Orange County, 1985-1993 (Box 1 (5-Affiliates), Folder 34)
    - Orange County, Individual Placement and Support, 2001 (Box 1 (5-Affiliates), Folder 35)
    - Orleans County, 1992-1993 (Box 1 (5-Affiliates), Folder 36)
    - Oswego County, 1988; 1991 (Box 1 (5-Affiliates), Folder 37)
    - Putnam County, 1992 (Box 1 (5-Affiliates), Folder 38)
    - Queens County, 1989; 1991 (Box 1 (5-Affiliates), Folder 39)
    - Rensselaer County, 1967-1996 (Box 1 (5-Affiliates), Folder 40)
    - Rockland County, 1987-1995 (Box 1 (5-Affiliates), Folder 41)
    - Rockland County, "Choosing a Psychotherapist", 1987 (Box 1 (5-Affiliates), Folder 42)
    - Rockland County, Early Intervention Projects, 1991; Undated (Box 1 (5-Affiliates), Folder 42)
    - Saratoga County, 1963-1996 (Box 2 (5-Affiliates), Folder 1)
    - Schuyler County, 1959-1965; 1985-1992 (Box 2 (5-Affiliates), Folder 2)
    - Sidney, 1996 (Box 2 (5-Affiliates), Folder 3)
    - Staten Island, 1968-1996 (Box 2 (5-Affiliates), Folder 4)
    - Steuben County, 1960-1963; 1991-1992 (Box 2 (5-Affiliates), Folder 5)
    - Staten Island, 1968-1996 (Box 2 (5-Affiliates), Folder 6)
    - Sullivan County, 1963-1996 (Box 2 (5-Affiliates), Folder 7)